Contact

keviethedreamer@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ keviethedreamer (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Education
Patient Outcomes

Certifications

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Experienced Provider (ACLS)

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Medical-Surgical Nursing (RN-BC)
NIH Stroke Scale

Kevin Jackson II, RN, BSN

Travel RN

Gallipolis, Ohio

Summary

Kevin Jackson II is a highly skilled, certified RN with over nine years of inpatient nursing experience that includes more than two years as a travel nurse and a career that comprises of a vast array of nursing focuses such as Intensive/Critical Care, Stepdown/ Interventional Recovery, Telemetry, Medical-Surgical, Longterm Care and Inpatient Rehab; experiences that have allowed Kevin to garner many different specific nursing skills such as pulling sheaths, etc. that make Kevin an excellent addition to any unit.

"If you have a light, then hold it up and let it shine. Would you make the choice to be your destiny, or let this lifetime pass you by? Only you can make it. What's yours is yours; no one can take it. If you have a dream, something you believe... it's time to set it free!" - Melanie Fiona

Experience

Kaiser Permanente Travel RN January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months) Los Angeles, California

Telemetry (Kaiser LAMC)

Agency: Aequor Healthcare Services

Charleston Area Medical Center Health System
Travel RN
August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months)

Trauma Stepdown/5S Trauma (5 South) (CAMC General)

Agency: Aequor Healthcare Services

Cabell Huntington Hospital Staff RN February 2018 - January 2019 (1 year)

Huntington, West Virginia

Stepdown (5 North)

Keck Medicine of USC

Travel RN

January 2017 - December 2017 (1 year)

Los Angeles, California

Telemetry Float Pool

Agency: Emerald Healthcare

Desert Regional Medical Center

Travel RN

October 2016 - January 2017 (4 months)

Palm Springs, California

ICU/PCU Float Pool

Agency: TravelMax (Maxim Healthcare Services)

Mercy Medical Center Merced Hospital

Travel RN

April 2016 - September 2016 (6 months)

Merced, California

MICU

Agency: MedWave Healthcare Staffing

Kaiser Permanente

Travel RN

January 2016 - March 2016 (3 months)

Redwood City, California

Neurological Observation Unit (NOU/Stepdown)

Agency: NurseChoice (AMN)

Via Christi Health

Travel RN

October 2015 - December 2015 (3 months)

Wichita, Kansas

Telemetry/Med-Surg (8 South East)

Agency: NurseChoice (AMN)

The Ohio State University Wexner Medical Center

Staff RN

January 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 8 months)

Columbus, Ohio

Telemetry/Med-Surg (11 East Rhodes)

Holzer Health System
Staff RN
April 2011 - April 2014 (3 years 1 month)
Gallipolis, Ohio

03/11 - 12/11 Inpatient Rehab

01/12 - 04/14 IRU (Interventional Recovery Unit/Stepdown) (Consisted of frequent, often weekly floating to ICU and/or Telemetry/Med-Surg units)

O'Bleness Memorial Hospital Staff RN June 2010 - March 2011 (10 months) Athens, Ohio

ICU

Education

Ohio University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2012)

University of Rio Grande and Rio Grande Community College Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (2008 - 2010)